[theme music playing]
[Nimfa] I may have done the wrong thing.
-But there's no turning back now.
-[Camia grunts]
-Hello, Ma'am Emilia!
-Nimfa!
[Ivy] The truth is that we came
to ask for your endorsement
so that Arnaldo could join your party.
[Arnaldo] I don't care
about the endorsement!
I'll form my own party for all I care,
just stop acting like a cheap whore--
How dare you say that to me?
[Emilia] Does your fiancée
really love you?
Maybe she brought you here…
-to set you up.
-Shut up!
Okay, go ahead. Follow her!
That way, you'll see that
she doesn't really love you.
Ivy, it's Nimfa. She's the one who
told Emilia that Lily is still alive.
[Arnaldo] How long have you been
meeting with Diego?
[Camia] Nimfa got away.
I'm sure she'll go to Emilia
and tell her who Ivy really is.
[Ivy] Diego is just a friend.
If you don't believe me,
if you think I'm betraying you,
let's just stop this.
We should call off our wedding.
You just broke my heart.
We should spend some time apart.
So, you're Mom's spy.
I need to tell her
something about Miss Ivy.
You shouldn't trust her.
She's just using you.
You need to know that Ivy is--
-That's not true!
-[gunshots]
[Diego] Nimfa is Emilia's spy.
She was bribed with money
and other things.
Emilia told her to spy on our party
and sabotage my campaign.
My daughter wouldn't do that!
[Ivy] You killed Nimfa?
[Arnaldo] I killed for you.
That's how much I love you.
We will only get married
if you believe me
when I say I'm not
a traitor to your family.
I'm worried because my spy
hasn't checked in with me yet.
Nimfa is dead, and I killed her.
Why did you do that?!
Don't you know that
I was using her to find out--
To find out what?!
What exactly do you want to know?!
Tell me! To chase some
evidence that doesn't exist
to ruin Ivy's reputation?!
Well, guess what?!
Your spy didn't discover a thing! Nothing!
I don't believe you!
Nimfa tried to call me several times!
If she didn't know anything,
then why would she call me?!
That's impossible!
I know she discovered something
about your beloved Ivy!
Well, I've nothing to say to you.
Well, except that she begged
for her life. That's it.
-Enough!
-Damn right, I've had enough!
I'm sick of all of you meddling
in my affairs, especially you!
Hey! You benefited from my interference!
Because of that,
I was able to intercept
Diego's campaign plans!
Get that through
that thick skull of yours!
Everything you do also
benefits you! Right?!
You wanted to know if
Ivy's funding their campaign.
Am I right?!
In spite of me telling you
to back off, you kept pushing!
You even went out of your way
to have her raped?!
Now, Nimfa is dead.
And, that is the price
you had to pay for what you did.
We're even.
[tense music playing]
Well, that cleared the air.
[Diego] That bastard!
He's rotten to the core!
Ivy, I'm going after Arnaldo.
I'll make him pay!
Please forgive me, Diego.
Because of me, Nimfa's gone.
That's not true.
Diego, Nimfa discovered my secret.
That secret put her life in danger.
That's why she was killed!
No. This wouldn't have happened to Nimfa
if it weren't for the Ardientes!
You did nothing wrong, Ivy.
Don't blame yourself.
We'll file a case against them.
But no one witnessed
Nimfa's murder, Diego.
Arnaldo already disposed of her body too.
[Ivy] Diego, if there's no
evidence, then there's no case.
[faucet running]
-[gunshots]
-[Arnaldo screaming]
[no audible dialogue]
[desolate music playing]
Dad…
the witnesses…
Nanny Carlotta…
And now, Nimfa…
They're just some of
the Ardientes' victims.
Tonight, I'm lighting a candle…
for Nimfa…
for all of them.
To pay my respects and extend my sympathy…
and to promise that it will not end here.
[Loring] Hey, there's food
at the back, okay?
Don't be shy. Help yourselves
to some coffee and food.
[man] Okay, ma'am.
-Here you go.
-Oh, thank you.
Oh, I'm really worried.
[sighs]
I really hope they find Nimfa,
so Diego won't feel sad anymore.
I hope so too. I wonder where Nimfa is.
According to Diego,
she ran away…
and headed to the
mansion of the Ardientes.
Hey, come here and have
something to eat, Diego.
[Loring] Come.
What's wrong, Diego?
Is there a problem?
Diego?
Nanny, Uncle…
There's something you need to know.
[man whistling]
This area's so filthy. Hey! Shoo!
There's a lot of trash here.
It's like this every day.
What's this? This thing is huge.
I wonder what's inside.
[gasps]
It's a hand!
Help! There's a corpse here!
Help! Everyone! Come here!
Everyone, help!
[man] There's a corpse here!
-What's wrong?!
-There's a body here!
-What?
-Oh, no.
-Miss Loring!
-I don't know!
-I saw a hand…
[man] …when I picked it up!
Miss Loring!
-Is this about Nimfa?
-Miss Loring!
[woman] Miss Loring!
There's a commotion outside.
They found a body!
-What?!
-A body!
[Pandoy] What?!
[woman 2] Call the police!
There's a body here! Police!
[Loring] What?!
[man] I don't know!
I was just getting the trash.
[Pandoy] Who-- Does anyone
know who dumped this here?
I don't know! I was just getting the trash
when I saw a hand!
And when I looked closer, I saw a corpse!
Who is this, Diego?!
Diego?!
[desolate music playing]
[Loring weeping]
[man] Oh, no.
[Loring] Nimfa!
[Loring crying]
It's Fernan! Fernan!
[Loring] What happened?
-Fernan!
-Nimfa!
-Nimfa! Nimfa!
-[Loring screams]
-Mister Fernan.
-Nimfa!
[Diego] Mister Fernan. Mister Fernan.
[Fernan weeping]
-Nimfa!
-Calm down, sir.
-[Fernan weeping]
-Please calm down.
She's my daughter!
Nimfa!
[Fernan weeping]
Nimfa! My dear!
Let me go, Diego!
Diego, please!
[Fernan weeping]
What did they do to my daughter?!
Nimfa!
[Loring] Miss Camia…
Who did this to you?!
Tell me!
Nimfa!
[indistinct chatter]
[Loring weeping]
-Take that away.
-The ambulance is here.
[Fernan] Nimfa!
-Nimfa!
-Come on. Carry her.
[Loring and Fernan weeping]
[Fernan] Nimfa!
Nimfa!
[tense music playing]
Nimfa, dear! Nimfa! Nimfa!
-Nimfa!
-Let's go.
Nimfa!
[ambulance siren blaring]
This is just the beginning, Diego.
[police officer] Do you know the victim?
Nimfa was my childhood friend.
-When did you last see her?
-We were together last night.
But she ran away.
I know who did this.
Arnaldo Ardiente killed her!
He killed my friend!
Okay, then. I'll need
your official statement,
and if your statement
matches the results of
the fingerprint test on the gun,
we'll know who the killer is.
Diego.
My daughter is gone!
[Loring] Get him some water. Fernan.
-Pandoy.
-Sit down. Sit down. Please.
-Mister Fernan.
-Sit. Sit down.
Here's the water.
-Fernan.
-Give me back my daughter!
[Fernan weeping]
My daughter!
Mister Fernan, drink this.
Fernan, drink some water.
I heard the Ardientes killed my daughter!
Is it because she's connected to Emilia?
Someone tell me the truth!
Mister Fernan, we don't have proof.
But you're right.
The Ardientes are responsible for this.
Don't worry.
-My poor daughter.
-We'll make them pay.
Their day will come.
[Camia] Diego…
of all the places here
in Poblacion Ardiente,
why did they put Nimfa's body
in front of your headquarters?
[ominous music playing]
I feel this was all planned.
I can only think of two things.
It's either they'll have
me killed or have me framed up.
[Diego] This can't happen.
I need to act fast.
Mister Fernan, don't worry.
I'll do everything to
bring justice to Nimfa's death.
My daughter…
[Fernan] Why…
Hon…
I was just thinking…
so many things have happened.
I'm so stressed out.
Then, I realized
that maybe we can speed up the wedding.
Speed it up?
I like it.
But, I'm actually curious
as to why you'd want that.
[upbeat music playing]
Because Nimfa's death…
made me realize life really is short.
That's why I want to get
married as soon as possible.
As soon as possible, hon.
I love you.
Oh, really?
You mean, you don't hate me
despite knowing that I was
the one who killed Nimfa?
No, hon.
Never.
Because you're the only
one who could do that.
And you only did that for me.
So, Arnaldo…
[sinister music playing]
I want us to get married right away.
I love you.
[sighs] What's with that look?
It's like you don't believe me.
No, I actually believe you.
-Really?
-I do.
Thank you.
[sinister music continues]
I love you.
I said I love you.
I love you too.
Hmm.
Arnaldo! Arnaldo!
[Claire] Diego! What are you doing here?!
Where's Arnaldo?
Do you remember the
last time you were here?
You never learn, do you?
Arnaldo! You monster!
What did you do to Nimfa?!
Nimfa?
I don't know what you're talking about.
You liar!
You think you can get away with this
just because you're the mayor?
I won't stop until I
make you pay for this!
-You bastard!
-[laughs viciously]
[Arnaldo chuckles]
-Diego…
-Hon…
No, I'm okay.
I was just about to say that…
if you want justice for Nimfa's death,
don't worry. You'll get it.
Soon.
[Arnaldo laughs viciously]
[Arnaldo] Whoa!
Take it easy. This coat's new.
[Arnaldo sighs]
I don't know what game
you're playing, Arnaldo.
But I promise you, I will take you down.
I'll have the last laugh.
[Ivy] Hon? Surprise!
-Hi, Honey!
-Hi!
-Mm…
-[Arnaldo] Uh…
What's this? Who are they?
Oh, um…
This is Charlie and Monet.
They're designers.
I want you to choose
your suit for our wedding.
Okay, but isn't it too early for that?
Excuse me.
Come on, hon. Too early?
We haven't even set
the date of our wedding.
Well then, let's set a date.
[moans]
But before that…
I want to get married as soon as possible
because I'm scared of Diego's threat.
But I know you can handle Diego, hon.
Especially when you said that
Nimfa's about to get justice.
The question is…
How?
Hon, sit down.
Don't worry about that, okay?
[nervous laugh]
Let me see your designs. Okay.
Help me choose, then.
Charlie, Monet, sit down.
[Arnaldo] Do you like this? It's green.
There are rumors going around that
the Ardiente family has an armory,
full of unlicensed and unregistered guns.
Good thing you reported this
to the Manila office.
Otherwise, this would've been ignored.
Detective, conspiracy
has become the norm here.
That's why we asked for your help.
And one more thing.
If the gun used to kill your friend
matches a gun in that armory,
that would be strong evidence
to incriminate the Ardientes,
not only in the killing of Nimfa.
We can trace various crimes
committed in this town
using those firearms.
Thank you, Attorney.
[detective] This is solid
evidence, Mr. Torillo.
This is our priority operation.
We'll raid this armory
as soon as possible.
[goon] Congressman, someone's coming!
They're armed! Special forces from Manila.
[rapid gunfire]
[suspenseful music playing]
The Ardientes are finally
going to pay for their crimes.
Open fire.
Buy us some time. Go!
Yes, sir.
Hurry up.
[suspenseful music continues]
-[gunshots]
-[man grunts]
[Julio] Faster.
[rapid gunfire]
Move! Move!
Search the area.
Sir, negative.
Okay. Move.
ARDIENTES' HIDDEN ARMORY RAIDED
Diego, look.
I know this will add to your good record
because you had their
hidden armory raided.
Atty. Fisher, we can
use this against them.
Let's add this to our evidence
against the Ardientes
once we open the case.
We are fine-tuning Arthur's testimony.
And yes, we can use that evidence.
We can open the case soon.
[Camia] Lily, I wish you were here.
We should've been celebrating with you.
Mom, it's okay.
The mere fact that you're all
happy makes me happy too.
[Ivy] Diego.
Thank you so much.
I'm very impressed by what you did.
Again, thank you.
We almost lost everything.
Because of that bastard, Diego.
Your inheritance…
the armory…
and everything in it.
We almost lost it.
Damn you, Diego.
If you think you can stop me
from carrying out my plans
because of that raid, you're wrong.
You got it all wrong.
[woman] I miss Nimfa.
Life really is short.
So, if you want to do
something, just do it.
To be fair, Nimfa did that.
Remember when we saw her with Diego?
[woman] I remember!
She said she loved Diego.
Too bad, Diego didn't like her.
He even pushed her.
That hurt Nimfa, you know.
No matter what she did,
Diego never seemed to like her.
I know.
Ladies…
-Was that true?
-Hi, Mayor.
-Hello, Mayor.
Uh, it seems like you two know
something interesting.
Could you share it with me over dinner?
[chuckles] Did you hear that?
Mayor invited us to dinner.
Sure, Mayor! What do you want to know?
Everything you know about Diego and Nimfa.
Sure.
-No problem.
-Let's go.
Wait, why did you use
matte lipstick on her
and glossy lipstick on me?
I want something like that.
Maybe they used glossy lipstick on you
because you have dry lips, Emilia.
But, if you want to use
my lipstick, no problem.
-Go on, use it on her.
-Yes, ma'am.
Yeah, I like it! It looks nice.
By the way, I noticed how nice
you've been to me lately.
Despite what I did
sending a spy to infiltrate Diego's group.
Aren't you offended?
Well, as much as I'd want to be,
it's not like your spy
accomplished anything.
She died.
I know! She's dead.
But, if Nimfa were alive,
I'm pretty sure she would've
found some dirt on you.
[laughs]
Emilia, we haven't even-- Go. Leave us.
Quit eavesdropping.
Emilia, we haven't even
recovered after what happened
at the Ardientes' armory.
Shouldn't we be sticking together
during times like this?
Future mother-in-law,
I even lent you my lipstick!
Okay.
Excuse me, Miss Aguas. You're up next.
-Okay.
-Go, you're needed inside.
What do you think? Do I look okay?
Yeah, you look fine.
[Ivy] Thanks! Excuse me.
Aunt Claire, come!
You know I really smell something fishy.
What do you mean?
I just know.
I can feel it, Auntie.
If Nimfa hadn't died,
she would've found dirt on that woman.
But, it doesn't matter.
I won't stop until I find
something about her.
By hook, or by crook.
A lot of people
are saying that this is going
to be the political wedding of the decade.
[giggles] Thank you.
But, you can't get away
without a little controversy.
Mayor Torillo,
the firearms in your possession
were all confiscated.
That was just a misunderstanding.
You know, whatever happens,
that won't affect our wedding
or my candidacy.
[woman] But there's a pending case
filed by your half-brother, Diego Torillo.
It won't affect our wedding
or my candidacy
because whoever dares
to clash with Arnaldo
-Ardiente Tor--
-Hon…
Hon.
[tense music playing]
Okay. Sorry.
-Next question, please.
-Okay.
[Ivy exhales]
Camera's ready to roll?
Let's begin, Mr. Torillo.
No matter how hard you try
to hide the truth,
it will come out eventually.
I did not publicize the information
regarding the Ardientes' armory
just to ruin the mayor's reputation.
I did it because
it was the right thing to do.
-It is illegal--
-[knocking on door]
Mr. Torillo, we have a
warrant for your arrest
for the murder of Nimfa Naig.
[Loring] What?!
[police officer] You have
the right to remain silent.
Everything you say or do
will be used against you.
-What?
-You have the right…
to an attorney.
If you can't afford one,
the government will provide one for you.
[Loring] What's this?
[tense music playing]
[camera shutter clicks]
[Loring] Wait a minute.
Those allegations aren't true.
You can't just arrest him.
If you do, there will be trouble.
I'm sure the Ardientes are behind this.
They're afraid of losing the election,
that's why they're framing Diego up.
-She's right!
-Yeah!
-[indistinct chatter]
-Calm down, everyone.
We're just doing our job.
-Please come with us.
-No!
-Hold on just a second!
-Nanny, Uncle, everyone…
I'm going with them.
But please don't worry,
we all know I'm innocent.
This is just a tactic used
by our enemies to bring us down.
We all know who really killed Nimfa.
It was Arnaldo Ardiente-Torillo,
and I will prove it.
-Let's go, officer.
-Cuff him.
You don't have to
because the innocent
never run away from the law.
Batch, don't worry.
We'll manage your campaign
while you're away.
-Thank you, Batch.
-Leave it to us.
-Nanny, Uncle…
-Take care of yourself.
Don't worry about me.
-Diego…
-All right.
-Let's get moving.
-Diego…
I'll go with you to the precinct.
Who knows where they might take you.
Sir, ma'am, I'll take care of him.
-Don't worry.
-Ma'am…
Everyone.
[Camia] Attorney, I need
to see you right away.
[camera shutter clicks]
-[Emilia] Papa!
-[Julio] Yes?
This day deserves a celebration.
[Arnaldo] Thank you.
-Emilia.
-Let's have champagne.
[pops bottle]
This is not necessary.
Why not, Papa?
You know, we should be celebrating now
because our victory is certain.
After what Arnaldo did to
Diego… [sighs in relief]
This election is just going to be easy.
As easy as stealing candy from a baby.
Hon, what did you do to him?
Why are you so bothered, Ivy?
Affected much?
[sighs]
-[Raul] Arnaldo!
-[Emilia] You should be.
Arnaldo. What did you do to Diego?
I had him arrested for Nimfa's murder.
[tense music playing]
Mr. Diego Torillo, sign this.
I'll take your mug shot afterward.
I won't sign anything
until I talk to my lawyer.
She'll be here soon.
The judge already signed
your commitment order.
And the mobile patrol
is on its way to pick you up.
That's where they put murderers like you.
Excuse me, but that's slander.
I could press charges against you
for what you said to my client.
Atty. Georgina Fisher,
counsel of Mister Torillo.
I'd like to speak
with my client privately.
And I don't need to explain to you
that you are obligated by the
law to grant us this request.
Deny us of this right and you'll be sorry.
I will add you to the list
of dishonest cops
who I've removed from their posts.
Excuse me.
Emilia, all I'm saying is,
it's a good thing he was able to…
seek justice for Nimfa's death.
I just can't believe Diego
could do such a thing.
Because it's true he wouldn't.
I know what you did, Arnaldo.
-You framed him up.
-You're right.
It was a frame-up.
And it was so easy.
All because your favorite son's an idiot.
[Arnaldo] You know what to tell the cops?
Mayor…
Don't worry. I've got your back.
Just don't make me mad.
The witnesses are ready.
Do you know where to bring
the girl's body?
Okay. Get on it.
Do you really think
this will work, Arnaldo?
It will hold him off for a while.
Long enough for me to win the election.
And who knows?
He might end up getting
into an accident in prison.
[chuckles]
That may be inevitable,
but it's better for you to play it safe.
I know.
Like I said, don't worry, Grandpa.
Everything's set.
It's your show.
[man] Your plane tickets to
Singapore are in there.
Go on a vacation first.
What will happen to Nimfa's case?
My boss will make sure
the perpetrator will go to jail.
Wait, who's your boss?
It's not important who he is.
But he will seek justice
for Nimfa's death.
Get inside the car.
-Give me an update.
-It's all set, boss.
Hey.
[scoffs] You look disappointed.
Turn that frown upside down.
Or would you rather I killed him instead?
[Emilia] Raul! Stop it! Raul!
-Hon!
-Go on!
-That's enough!
-What?!
-Raul!
-What?! Huh?! Come here.
-Come here!
[Ivy] Hon! Emilia, stop Raul!
-Raul!
-I'll kill him!
-Stop right there!
-Hon!
You bastard! What?!
[Emilia gasping]
[Emilia] Raul! Raul, wait!
Don't go!
You will pay for this!
Hon?
You insolent piece of shit!
-Are you okay?
-I'm okay.
-Hon.
[Georgina] An eyewitness
and the body of the victim
at your headquarters?
They have a very compelling case
against you, Diego.
Attorney, I'm being framed.
Arnaldo's behind all this.
He wants to taint my reputation,
so he can win the election.
But attorney, the truth is…
Arnaldo killed Nimfa.
Ivy told me herself.
Do you have this confession?
Well, it's hard to prove it
without evidence.
But, you're right.
He does have motive to discredit you.
Because the Ardientes are scared of Diego.
They know that he can defeat Arnaldo.
Diego, you have the public's support.
And we'll use the support of the people
to spin this case against the Ardientes.
We'll hold a press conference.
So you can air your version of the story.
We'll beat the Ardientes to it,
so your name won't be ruined any further.
But, I'm sorry, Diego. I can't
get you out of here for now.
I will try to delay your transfer
to the provincial jail,
and I will do my best
to have your case dismissed.
Attorney, thank you very much.
Thank you, attorney.
DIEGO FOR THE NEW ARDIENTE
[Pandoy sighs deeply]
Those Ardientes are pure evil.
They'll do anything to get ahead.
They'll try to manipulate
anyone to believe that Diego is a killer.
What if Diego really killed my daughter?
-What?
-Fernan.
Fernan.
You really believe Diego
is capable of killing someone?
[Pandoy] After everything
he's done for us?
He's just like Miss Aguas!
She may have done a lot for the farmers,
but who is she supporting?
Isn't she backing the Ardientes?
There's a witness against Diego.
No one will testify in court
if they aren't telling the truth.
You really think it's impossible, Fernan?
The Ardientes can make
the impossible possible!
Possible or impossible,
I don't care about that!
I just want someone to pay
for my daughter's death.
They will!
And if it is Diego,
prison won't be enough as punishment.
Fernan!
Mister Fernan.
[Pandoy sighs heavily]
[indistinct chattering]
My father was way out of line.
One more wrong move
and I'll finish him off.
Hon. Do you hear what you're saying?
He's your dad.
Well, he's useless to me.
And to this world.
He's better off as fertilizer,
just like Nimfa and, soon enough, Diego.
Ouch!
What's wrong?
-Hey! What's your problem?
-You are!
You're my problem.
See?
Look at yourself.
You can't help but show
your concern for Diego.
You're thinking of him again.
I'm thinking of you!
I'm concerned about you!
You're getting out of control.
You're turning murder into a hobby!
I'm just scared
because once we're married…
What if I mess up the dish
I'm cooking or something?
You might just shoot me!
I could never hurt you.
I told you I would never hurt you.
[sighs] Hon, I'm so confused.
I don't know because lately, I feel like…
I don't know you anymore.
It's like you have so many secrets.
What if you killed somebody else
other than Nimfa?
So, tell me, hon.
Aside from Nimfa…
have you killed anyone else?
Hon, tell me.
I don't want any secrets.
[Carlotta screaming]
Have you killed anyone else?
[tense music playing]
No.
I haven't killed anyone aside from Nimfa.
And I'm sorry for sounding
like a psychopath.
I don't want you to be afraid of me.
I want you to feel safe with me.
I sent Diego to jail
so I'd stop feeling jealous.
I don't want to be angry with you anymore.
So, I'll make sure…
that he never gets out of jail.
That way, he won't bother us again.
I thought Raul had changed, Papa.
I thought he'd forgotten
about that bastard.
I thought he was on our side!
Blood is thicker than water, Emilia.
But, Auntie, Arnaldo is also his son.
Why can't he love his two sons equally?
Because he loved…
Diego's mother more than you!
Just like all the other women
he has loved more than you.
All the women in his life!
You're so pathetic!
For years, I have watched you!
Begging, begging! Pleading for his love!
But that Raul has never
had any love to give you.
What that man has given you…
is pain.
Pain for you, and for this family!
Congressman, your car is ready.
Good.
Emilia.
As lovesick as you are,
you're still my daughter, and I love you.
And tonight,
I will end your misery.
Papa, what do you mean?
Just prepare a beautiful black dress.
And call your religious
female friends if you have any.
No, Papa. You can't--
[Julio] Because Raul's soul
will need a lot of people…
-to pray for him.
-No, Papa! Please, don't!
Please! Papa!
Papa!
Emilia, where are you going?
I will save my husband, Auntie.
Emilia!
[camera shutter clicks]
Diego.
Don't worry. We'll look into your case,
so you won't have to stay here for long.
That's right.
Your transfer to the
provincial jail is postponed.
You're safer here.
Aunt Camia, please take care of
Nanny Loring and Uncle Pandoy.
Tell them I'm fine.
About Ivy… I know her.
She'll find a way to get me out of here.
Tell her not to do anything
that might put her in danger.
Diego, keep your guard up here.
-Thank you, Aunt Camia.
-All right.
Attorney.
[Raul] Diego. Son.
-Dad?
-How are you?
I won't take long, sir.
-What are you doing here, Dad?
[Raul breathes heavily]
Are you sure you don't want
to spend the night here with me?
My wounds will heal faster
if you stay here.
Your wounds won't heal, hon.
Because if I lay down beside you,
I might get wild.
Well, that's what I like.
Wild.
[exhales sharply] Not now.
I know you're still furious
at your dad and Diego.
You just might end up hurting me, instead.
Okay, you're punishing me.
I get it.
-I'm punishing you?
-Mm-hm.
No, hon.
Because you wouldn't want…
to be punished by Ivy Aguas.
[tense music playing]
-Ivy.
-[chuckles]
-[Arnaldo chuckles]
-Sorry, hon.
I'm just like this when I'm in love.
Well, we only have to suffer a bit.
It's almost the wedding.
I can't wait.
Me either.
[moans]
-Good night.
[car engine turns over]
Raul. What are you doing here?
I'm helping my son get out of here.
Son, don't worry.
I'll find a good lawyer
to help you get out of here, okay?
Thanks, Dad. But I've got a good lawyer.
Raul. I'll take care of it.
We can solve Diego's case faster
if you won't get involved.
Just go back to hiding
behind the Ardientes.
But here's the thing, Camia. He's my son.
So I have the right
to help him get out of here.
Yes, you're his father.
A father who doesn't know how to be one.
A father who blindly
follows the Ardientes.
[scoffs] I don't know what your
-problem is.
-Dad. Dad.
Please. You should leave.
-I'll prove it to you.
-You won't prove anything to me
or anyone as long as you're
under the Ardientes' thumb.
-Of course, he wouldn't…
-Emilia.
leave our side.
-You know why, Camia?
-Emilia.
Because he's all mine.
Grandpa?
[phone ringing]
-Arnaldo.
-Grandpa, where are you?
Oh, I'm at Raul's final resting place.
Wait for me. I'll be there.
I want to get back at that bastard.
[sighs] No, no, no.
You sit this one out, Arnaldo.
I don't think you should see this.
You might end up
feeling sorry for your father
after what I'll do to him,
or even stop me.
Besides,
you've got too much blood
on your hands already.
I think it's about time I took over
the dirty jobs once again
just like this one.
Well, make sure you punish him good.
Oh, don't worry. I will.
In the meantime,
keep an eye on Miss Aguas, okay?
[exhales sharply]
Okay.
Mm?
Congressman. We found where
Ma'am Emilia and Raul are.
Good.
Bring both of them here.
-Now.
-Yes, sir.
[dramatic music playing]
They framed me
for the murder of Nimfa Naig.
Why would they do that to you?
To ensure that their side will win.
Let's do a pre-election survey.
Whoever wins there is the one
who's telling the truth.
Now, who are they going to choose?
A criminal or an honest
politician like me?
[Julio] How did this dog beat you?
[Camia] He needs to get out of that prison
because I know the Ardientes
are plotting to get rid of him.
[Ivy] I have the evidence
that will set him free.
[Arnaldo on voice memo]
No. I haven't killed anyone
aside from Nimfa.
I will tell the world that I am Lily.
[theme music playing]